thenamemeaning.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy policy - The Name Meaning

The Name Meaning – Baby names, boy names, girl names, name meanings

This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users. The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by this Website and how it is used.

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Website collects, by itself or through thi

rd parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data, first name, last name, and email address.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this Website.  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this Website is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this Website to provide its services. In cases where this Website specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Website or by the owners of third-party services used by this Website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Website and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Methods of processing

The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this Website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

### Legal basis of processing

The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

  * Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations, the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
  * provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
  * processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
  * processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
  * Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.

In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any

other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

## Retention time

Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

  * Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
  * Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.

The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

## No Information Collected from Children.

We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately removed from any access. Because it does not collect such information, this Website has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. This Website has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).

## The purposes of processing

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Advertising, Contacting the User, Content commenting, Data transfer outside the EU, Displaying content from external platforms, Content performance and features testing (A/B testing), Traffic optimization and distribution and SPAM protection.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Advertising

This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Website, possibly based on User interests.  
This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.  
Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

Some of our digital advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, each of which offer a single location to opt-out of certain ad targeting from member companies. To learn more about interest-based advertising generally as well as your options for opting out, please visit [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [About Ads](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own website at [FTC Privacy Site](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/privacy-identity). Please keep in mind that even if you opt-out of receiving ads tailored to your apparent interests, you will continue to see ads from online advertising networks. However, those networks will not be able to apply any of your apparent ad preferences and the ads that you see therefore may be less relevant to your interests.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this Website.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this Website and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

You can use [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to manage the Google ads you see and opt out of Ads Personalization.

##### Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google AdSense

On this website, the controller has integrated Google AdSense. Google AdSense is an online service which allows the placement of advertising on third-party sites. Google AdSense is based on an algorithm that selects advertisements displayed on third-party sites to match with the content of the respective third-party site. Google AdSense allows an interest-based targeting of the Internet user, which is implemented by means of generating individual user profiles.

The operating company of Google’s AdSense component is Alphabet Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.

The purpose of Google’s AdSense component is the integration of advertisements on our website. Google AdSense places a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. The definition of cookies is explained above. With the setting of the cookie, Alphabet Inc. is enabled to analyze the use of our website. With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and into which a Google AdSense component is integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject will automatically submit data through the Google AdSense component for the purpose of online advertising and the settlement of commissions to Alphabet Inc. During the course of this technical procedure, the enterprise Alphabet Inc. gains knowledge of personal data, such as the IP address of the data subject, which serves Alphabet Inc., inter alia, to understand the origin of visitors and clicks and subsequently create commission settlements.

The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent Alphabet Inc. from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. Additionally, cookies already in use by Alphabet Inc. may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.

Furthermore, Google AdSense also uses so-called tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a miniature graphic that is embedded in web pages to enable a log file recording and a log file analysis through which a statistical analysis may be performed. Based on the embedded tracking pixels, Alphabet Inc. is able to determine if and when a website was opened by a data subject, and which links were clicked on by the data subject. Tracking pixels serve, inter alia, to analyze the flow of visitors on a website.

Through Google AdSense, personal data and information—which also includes the IP address, and is necessary for the collection and accounting of the displayed advertisements—is transmitted to Alphabet Inc. in the United States of America. These personal data will be stored and processed in the United States of America. The Alphabet Inc. may disclose the collected personal data through this technical procedure to third parties.

Google AdSense is further explained under the following link https://www.google.com/intl/en/adsense/start/.

#### DoubleClick for Publishers (DFP), DoubleClick Ad Exchange (AdX) and AdMob

We use Google’s DoubleClick for Publishers (DFP), DoubleClick Ad Exchange (AdX), AdMob, and AdSense to serve ads to our users based on their visit to the Site and/or other sites on the Internet. We use Google DART to serve ads on the Site. Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may [opt-out](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

#### Media.Net Advertising Ltd.

Media.Net is an advertising service provided by Media.Net Advertising Ltd.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

We use Media.net Advertising Ltd. to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site and to display ads to users on our Site. For information about Media.net and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Statement](https://www.media.net/en/privacy-policy). You may opt-out of receiving personalized ads from Media.net and other third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or who follow the DAA Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising using their respective opt-out tools. The NAI’s opt-out tool can be found here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> and the DAA’s opt-out tool can be found here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

For more details including [Opt Out](https://www.media.net/en/privacy-policy) requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [Privacy Policy](https://www.media.net/en/privacy-policy) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@media.net](mailto:privacy@media.net).

#### Amazon.com & Amazon.uk

We use Amazon to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site and to display ads to users on our Site. For information about Amazon and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Statement](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496). You may opt-out of Amazon’s collection of data via your browser by visiting the [Amazon Advertising Preferences Opt-out](https://www.amazon.com/gp/dra/info).

#### ShareASale

We use ShareASale, an affiliate marketing network that is operated by ShareASale.com inc. For information about ShareASale and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](http://www.shareasale.com/w3c/policy.html).

#### Sovrn

sovrn is an advertising service provided by sovrn Holdings, Inc..

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

We use sovrn Holdings, Inc. to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site and to display ads to users on our Site. For information about sovrn and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy-eu/) _EU_.

### Third Party Websites

We may link to third party websites from our own Site. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party websites or their use of your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites or ads and we are not responsible for the content found on or the actions or privacy practices employed by any other website or app.

The Site may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, such as Facebook (facebook.com), Google+ (plus.google.com), Twitter (twitter.com), and Pinterest (pinterest.com). The social media sites may receive data when you visit a website that has plugins. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a social plugin such as a Facebook Like button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information to a third-party operating a plug-in on this website, then this third-party may recognize you on the Site. Your use of social media plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours.

#### Affiliate Links – Advertising Disclosure

If you purchase a product or service linked from this Site, we may receive an “affiliate commission”. We are disclosing this in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s 16 CFR, Part 255: “Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising” and also in accordance to amazon associates programme operating agreement.

#### Amazon

We are participants in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

#### Amazon UK

We are participants in the Amazon EU Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.co.uk.

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

**Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google Analytics (with anonymization function)**

On this website, the controller has integrated the component of Google Analytics (with the anonymizer function). Google Analytics is a web analytics service. Web analytics is the collection, gathering, and analysis of data about the behavior of visitors to websites. A web analysis service collects, inter alia, data about the website from which a person has come (the so-called referrer), which sub-pages were visited, or how often and for what duration a sub-page was viewed. Web analytics are mainly used for the optimization of a website and in order to carry out a cost-benefit analysis of Internet advertising.

The operator of the Google Analytics component is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.

For the web analytics through Google Analytics the controller uses the application “_gat. _anonymizeIp”. By means of this application the IP address of the Internet connection of the data subject is abridged by Google and anonymised when accessing our websites from a Member State of the European Union or another Contracting State to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.

The purpose of the Google Analytics component is to analyze the traffic on our website. Google uses the collected data and information, inter alia, to evaluate the use of our website and to provide online reports, which show the activities on our websites, and to provide other services concerning the use of our Internet site for us.

Google Analytics places a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. The definition of cookies is explained above. With the setting of the cookie, Google is enabled to analyze the use of our website. With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and into which a Google Analytics component was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject will automatically submit data through the Google Analytics component for the purpose of online advertising and the settlement of commissions to Google. During the course of this technical procedure, the enterprise Google gains knowledge of personal information, such as the IP address of the data subject, which serves Google, inter alia, to understand the origin of visitors and clicks, and subsequently create commission settlements.

The cookie is used to store personal information, such as the access time, the location from which the access was made, and the frequency of visits of our website by the data subject. With each visit to our Internet site, such personal data, including the IP address of the Internet access used by the data subject, will be transmitted to Google in the United States of America. These personal data are stored by Google in the United States of America. Google may pass these personal data collected through the technical procedure to third parties.

The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent Google Analytics from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. In addition, cookies already in use by Google Analytics may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.

In addition, the data subject has the possibility of objecting to a collection of data that are generated by Google Analytics, which is related to the use of this website, as well as the processing of this data by Google and the chance to preclude any such. For this purpose, the data subject must download a browser add-on under the link https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and install it. This browser add-on tells Google Analytics through a JavaScript, that any data and information about the visits of Internet pages may not be transmitted to Google Analytics. The installation of the browser add-ons is considered an objection by Google. If the information technology system of the data subject is later deleted, formatted, or newly installed, then the data subject must reinstall the browser add-ons to disable Google Analytics. If the browser add-on was uninstalled by the data subject or any other person who is attributable to their sphere of competence, or is disabled, it is possible to execute the reinstallation or reactivation of the browser add-ons.

Further information and the applicable data protection provisions of Google may be retrieved under https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ and under http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html. Google Analytics is further explained under the following Link https://www.google.com/analytics/.

### Contact form (this Website)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Website to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name and last name.

This Website contains information that enables a quick electronic contact with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or via a contact form, the personal data transmitted by the data subject are automatically stored. Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the data controller are stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject. There is no transfer of this personal data to third parties.

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

##### Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google+

On this website, the controller has integrated the Google+ button as a component. Google+ is a so-called social network. A social network is a social meeting place on the Internet, an online community, which usually allows users to communicate with each other and interact in a virtual space. A social network may serve as a platform for the exchange of opinions and experiences, or enable the Internet community to provide personal or business-related information. Google+ allows users of the social network to include the creation of private profiles, upload photos and network through friend requests.

The operating company of Google+ is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this website, which is operated by the controller and on which a Google+ button has been integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject automatically downloads a display of the corresponding Google+ button of Google through the respective Google+ button component. During the course of this technical procedure, Google is made aware of what specific sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject. More detailed information about Google+ is available under https://developers.google.com/+/.

If the data subject is logged in at the same time to Google+, Google recognizes with each call-up to our website by the data subject and for the entire duration of his or her stay on our Internet site, which specific sub-pages of our Internet page were visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the Google+ button and Google matches this with the respective Google+ account associated with the data subject.

If the data subject clicks on the Google+ button integrated on our website and thus gives a Google+ 1 recommendation, then Google assigns this information to the personal Google+ user account of the data subject and stores the personal data. Google stores the Google+ 1 recommendation of the data subject, making it publicly available in accordance with the terms and conditions accepted by the data subject in this regard. Subsequently, a Google+ 1 recommendation given by the data subject on this website together with other personal data, such as the Google+ account name used by the data subject and the stored photo, is stored and processed on other Google services, such as search-engine results of the Google search engine, the Google account of the data subject or in other places, e.g. on Internet pages, or in relation to advertisements. Google is also able to link the visit to this website with other personal data stored on Google. Google further records this personal information with the purpose of improving or optimizing the various Google services.

Through the Google+ button, Google receives information that the data subject visited our website, if the data subject at the time of the call-up to our website is logged in to Google+. This occurs regardless of whether the data subject clicks or doesn’t click on the Google+ button.

If the data subject does not wish to transmit personal data to Google, he or she may prevent such transmission by logging out of his Google+ account before calling up our website.

Further information and the data protection provisions of Google may be retrieved under https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. More references from Google about the Google+ 1 button may be obtained under https://developers.google.com/+/web/buttons-policy.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy).

##### Data protection provisions about the application and use of Twitter

On this website, the controller has integrated components of Twitter. Twitter is a multilingual, publicly-accessible microblogging service on which users may publish and spread so-called ‘tweets,’ e.g. short messages, which are limited to 280 characters. These short messages are available for everyone, including those who are not logged on to Twitter. The tweets are also displayed to so-called followers of the respective user. Followers are other Twitter users who follow a user’s tweets. Furthermore, Twitter allows you to address a wide audience via hashtags, links or retweets.

The operating company of Twitter is Twitter, Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a Twitter component (Twitter button) was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject is automatically prompted to download a display of the corresponding Twitter component of Twitter. Further information about the Twitter buttons is available under https://about.twitter.com/de/resources/buttons. During the course of this technical procedure, Twitter gains knowledge of what specific sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject. The purpose of the integration of the Twitter component is a retransmission of the contents of this website to allow our users to introduce this web page to the digital world and increase our visitor numbers.

If the data subject is logged in at the same time on Twitter, Twitter detects with every call-up to our website by the data subject and for the entire duration of their stay on our Internet site which specific sub-page of our Internet page was visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the Twitter component and associated with the respective Twitter account of the data subject. If the data subject clicks on one of the Twitter buttons integrated on our website, then Twitter assigns this information to the personal Twitter user account of the data subject and stores the personal data.

Twitter receives information via the Twitter component that the data subject has visited our website, provided that the data subject is logged in on Twitter at the time of the call-up to our website. This occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on the Twitter component or not. If such a transmission of information to Twitter is not desirable for the data subject, then he or she may prevent this by logging off from their Twitter account before a call-up to our website is made.

The applicable data protection provisions of Twitter may be accessed under https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en.

#### Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).

##### Data protection provisions about the application and use of Pinterest

On this website, the controller has integrated components of Pinterest Inc. Pinterest is a so-called social network. A social network is an Internet social meeting place, an online community that allows users to communicate and interact with each other in a virtual space. A social network may serve as a platform for the exchange of opinions and experiences, or allow the Internet community to provide personal or company-related information. Pinterest enables the users of the social network to publish, inter alia, picture collections and individual pictures as well as descriptions on virtual pinboards (so-called pins), which can then be shared by other user’s (so-called re-pins) or commented on.

The operating company of Pinterest is Pinterest Inc., 808 Brannan Street, San Francisco, CA 94103, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a Pinterest component (Pinterest plug-in) was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject automatically prompted to download through the respective Pinterest component a display of the corresponding Pinterest component. Further information on Pinterest is available under https://pinterest.com/. During the course of this technical procedure, Pinterest gains knowledge of what specific sub-page of our website is visited by the data subject.

If the data subject is logged in at the same time on Pinterest, Pinterest detects with every call-up to our website by the data subject—and for the entire duration of their stay on our Internet site—which specific sub-page of our Internet page was visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the Pinterest component and associated with the respective Pinterest account of the data subject. If the data subject clicks on one of the Pinterest buttons, integrated on our website, then Pinterest assigns this information to the personal Pinterest user account of the data subject and stores the personal data.

Pinterest receives information via the Pinterest component that the data subject has visited our website, provided that the data subject is logged in at Pinterest at the time of the call-up to our website. This occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on the Pinterest component or not. If such a transmission of information to Pinterest is not desirable for the data subject, then he or she may prevent this by logging off from their Pinterest account before a call-up to our website is made.

The data protection guideline published by Pinterest, which is available under https://about.pinterest.com/privacy-policy, provides information on the collection, processing and use of personal data by Pinterest.

#### YouTube button and social widgets (Google Inc.)

The YouTube button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the YouTube social network provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

#### Data protection provisions about the application and use of Tumblr

On this website, the controller has integrated components of Tumblr. Tumblr is a platform that allows users to create and run a blog. A blog is a web-based, generally publicly-accessible portal on which one or more people called bloggers or web bloggers may post articles or write down thoughts in so-called blogposts. For example, in a Tumblr blog the user can publish text, images, links, and videos, and spread them in the digital space. Furthermore, Tumblr users may import content from other websites into their own blog.

The operating company of Tumblr is Tumblr, Inc., 35 East 21st St, Ground Floor, New York, NY 10010, UNITED STATES.

Through each call to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a Tumblr component (Tumblr button) has been integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject causes automatically the download of a display of the corresponding Tumblr component of Tumblr. Learn more about the Tumblr-buttons that are available under https://www.tumblr.com/buttons. During the course of this technical procedure, Tumblr becomes aware of what concrete sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject. The purpose of the integration of the Tumblr component is a retransmission of the contents of this website to allow our users to introduce this web page to the digital world and to increase our visitor numbers.

If the data subject is logged in at Tumblr, Tumblr detects with every call-up to our website by the data subject—and for the entire duration of their stay on our Internet site—which specific sub-page of our Internet page was visited by the data subject. This information is collected through the Tumblr component and associated with the respective Tumblr account of the data subject. If the data subject clicks on one of the Tumblr buttons, integrated on our website, then Tumblr assigns this information to the personal Tumblr user account of the data subject and stores the personal data.

Tumblr receives information via the Tumblr component that the data subject has visited our website, provided that the data subject is logged in at Tumblr at the time of the call-up to our website. This occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on the Tumblr component or not. If such a transfer of information to Tumblr is not desirable for the data subject, then he or she may prevent this by logging off from their Tumblr account before a call-up to our website is made.

The applicable data protection provisions of Tumblr may be accessed under https://www.tumblr.com/policy/en/privacy.

### Content performance and features testing (A/B testing)

The services contained in this section allow the Owner to track and analyze the User response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of this Website.

#### Google Website Optimizer (Google Inc.)

Google Website Optimizer is an A/B testing service provided by Google Inc.  
Google may use Personal Data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

### SPAM protection

This type of service analyzes the traffic of this Website, potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.

#### Akismet (Automattic Inc.)

Akismet is a SPAM protection service provided by Automattic Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

#### Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)

Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.  
The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

### Traffic optimization and distribution

This type of service allows this Website to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.  
Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between this Website and the User’s browser.  
Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred.

#### CloudFlare (Cloudflare)

CloudFlare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by CloudFlare Inc.  
The way CloudFlare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).

#### StackPath LLC

We use Stackpath as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by StackPath LLC. The way Stackpath is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about Stackpath and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.stackpath.com/privacy-statement/)

#### KeyCDN

We use KeyCDN as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by proinity LLC. The way KeyCDN is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about KeyCDN and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.keycdn.com/privacy)

### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Website.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

#### Comment system managed directly (this Website)

This Website has its own internal content comment system.

Personal Data collected: email address, first name, last name and website.

### Displaying content from external platforms

This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

##### Data protection provisions about the application and use of YouTube

On this website, the controller has integrated components of YouTube. YouTube is an Internet video portal that enables video publishers to set video clips and other users free of charge, which also provides free viewing, review and commenting on them. YouTube allows you to publish all kinds of videos, so you can access both full movies and TV broadcasts, as well as music videos, trailers, and videos made by users via the Internet portal.

The operating company of YouTube is YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, UNITED STATES. The YouTube, LLC is a subsidiary of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, UNITED STATES.

With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and on which a YouTube component (YouTube video) was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject is automatically prompted to download a display of the corresponding YouTube component. Further information about YouTube may be obtained under https://www.youtube.com/yt/about/en/. During the course of this technical procedure, YouTube and Google gain knowledge of what specific sub-page of our website was visited by the data subject.

If the data subject is logged in on YouTube, YouTube recognizes with each call-up to a sub-page that contains a YouTube video, which specific sub-page of our Internet site was visited by the data subject. This information is collected by YouTube and Google and assigned to the respective YouTube account of the data subject.

YouTube and Google will receive information through the YouTube component that the data subject has visited our website, if the data subject at the time of the call to our website is logged in on YouTube; this occurs regardless of whether the person clicks on a YouTube video or not. If such a transmission of this information to YouTube and Google is not desirable for the data subject, the delivery may be prevented if the data subject logs off from their own YouTube account before a call-up to our website is made.

YouTube’s data protection provisions, available at https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/, provide information about the collection, processing and use of personal data by YouTube and Google.

#### Google Fonts (Google Inc.)

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

Further information about handling user data, can be found at <https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq> and in Google’s privacy policy at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

#### Google Maps

We use Google Maps service, a service provided by Google Inc. Further information about handling visitor’s data, can be found in the data protection declaration of Google at <https://policies.google.com/privacy>.

#### MailChimp

We use Mailchimp, as a marketing automation platform and an email marketing service provided by Rocket Science Group. If you sign up for our newsletter, which is administered through Mailchimp, or if you register for our site, we will store some of your information, including your email address, IP address and certain information about the links you click within the emails we send you, on a Mailchimp server. Neither we nor Mailchimp will ever sell your email address or share it with any other party, unless we are legally compelled to do so. If you contact Mailchimp directly regarding your subscription to our newsletter, Mailchimp may contact you directly; otherwise, Mailchimp will never contact you. Only authorized Mailchimp employees have access to our subscriber list. You are always free to unsubscribe from our newsletter, but as long as you are registered with us we may use Mailchimp to send you information about your account. You can find out more about how MailChimp collects and stores your information at <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>.

#### Gravatar

We use the Gravatar service provided by Automattic inc. When visitors leave comments on the site an anonymized string created from their email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service. After approval of the comment, the profile picture which is provided by Gravatar will be publicly visible in the context of the comment. For information about Gravatar and how it collects and processes data, please visit its privacy policy: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>

#### Jetpack

We use Jetpack, a tool for statistical evaluation of accesses by visitors that is operated by Automattic, Inc., using a tracking technology by Quantcast Inc. You can opt-out to the collection and use of the data by Quantcast at <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>. You can find out more about how Jetpack and Quantacast collect and process data by visiting their respective privacy policy pages at <https://jetpack.com/support/privacy/> and <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>

### Data transfer outside the EU

The Owner is allowed to transfer Personal Data collected within the EU to third countries (i.e. any country not part of the EU) only pursuant to a specific legal basis. Any such Data transfer is based on one of the legal bases described below.  
Users can inquire with the Owner to learn which legal basis applies to which specific service.

#### Data transfer from the EU and/or Switzerland to the U.S based on Privacy Shield (this Website)

If this is the legal basis, the transfer of Personal Data from the EU or Switzerland to the US is carried out according to the EU – U.S. and Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield.  
In particular, Personal Data is transferred to services that self-certify under the Privacy Shield framework and therefore guarantee an adequate level of protection of such transferred Data. All services are listed within the relevant section of this document and those that adhere to Privacy Shield can be singled out by checking their privacy policy and possibly also by specifically checking for Privacy Shield adherence in the official Privacy Shield List. Privacy Shield also specifically guarantees rights to Users which can be found in its most current form on the website run by the US Department of Commerce.  
Personal Data may be transferred from within the EU or Switzerland to the U.S. to services that are not, or not anymore, part of Privacy Shield, only based on other valid legal grounds. Users can ask the Owner to learn about such legal grounds.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data.

### Service Providers

We may use third parties to help operate our website, authenticate users and deliver products and services, and may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our service providers, vendors, suppliers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Service (such as website or database hosting companies, authentication providers, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, this Website makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Registered users

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time. Website administrators can also see and edit that information. If you have an account on the Site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded data (EXIF data) included.

### Non-Personal Information We Collect

We may also collect information about you that is not personal information. When you access the Site, create an account and/or submit information, we may collect information such as your communication and other preferences, information about your computer, devices and Internet connection, IP address, browser, operating system, referring URL, metadata, specific pages that you access on the Site or prior to or after visiting the Site, the length of time you spend at the Site, and other general information about our visitors. This information, on its own, cannot be used to identify you. We may also collect non-personal information through the use of cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts, and other similar technologies, as further discussed below.

### Location Data

We may receive information about your device location when you access the Site. Your location data may be based on your IP address. We use location data in connection with providing the Site and to help improve user experience with the Site.

## Use of Information

We may freely use non-personal information or aggregate information for any lawful purpose. We also may use any information collected on or through our Site, including your personal information, (“Collected Information”) for various purposes. We and our third-party service providers may use Collected Information to:

  * help administer the Site and the servers that provide the Site;
  * generate statistical information;
  * market, promote or advertise the Site, the Content or our subscription services;
  * monitor and analyze Site traffic and usage patterns;
  * improve the Site’s content and content delivery, including any online content, materials, and services that we describe or make available on the Site;
  * register and administer your membership in our subscription service;
  * provide customer service and support;
  * verify communications from you, respond to your inquiries and otherwise communicate with you;
  * enforce our Terms of Service and contracts with third parties;
  * prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities or to otherwise comply with applicable laws and regulations; and
  * for any other purpose that is permissible or required under the law, that is disclosed to you at the point of collection of personal information, or for which you provide your prior consent.

We may specifically use IP addresses to provide aggregated data to advertisers about the volume of usage on the Site, to determine your general (but not precise) geographic location, to create and segment audiences and otherwise to target advertising, and to help identify and log potential malicious use of our Site.

We may also use Collected Information and the associated statistical data we and our third party service providers generate to deliver targeted advertisements to you and other visitors of the Site. We and our third party service providers may store Collected Information for as long as needed for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy, which may be indefinitely.

## Disclosure of Your Information – Law Enforcement

We may freely share and disclose aggregated and other non-personal information (including anonymized information and other non-personal information that is automatically collected as you navigate through and use the Site) without restriction as permitted by law. In particular, we may share Collected Information with certain of our third party service providers (e.g., our web hosting provider whose server logs collect the non-personal information described above) in order to provide the Site to you. We may also share Collected Information with some of our business and marketing partners in furthering our mission as an organization or delivering the content, materials, and services available on or through the Site to you. We and our third party service providers may also produce reports on Site traffic, usage patterns, and similar data generated from non-personal Collected Information, and we may share these reports with our business and marketing partners and others.

We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify you and we may use and disclose any information about or relating to you, including any personal information about you, to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order, search warrant, subpoena, or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) otherwise fulfill a government or law enforcement request for information; (4) establish, defend or exercise our legal rights; (5) protect or defend the Site, users, or our subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their respective officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, licensors, and partners, in connection with any actual or alleged legal action, claim or dispute; (6) respond to claims that any posting or other content of our Site violates the rights of third parties, including without limitation providing information necessary to satisfy the notice and counter-notice procedures pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act; (7) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our Site’s users or the general public; or (8) enforce compliance with our Terms of Service or other contractual obligations.

If all or part of the Site is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, we will transfer Collected Information to such entity as part of that transaction.

Every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may contract for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving the Site or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

## Security of Information

We make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep the Site secure, and we take reasonable steps to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse, alteration and destruction of the personal information under our control. We recommend that you use anti-virus software, anti-malware, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats. If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us immediately.

## Cookies And Tracking Technologies

### General Use

The Internet pages of this Website use cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser.

Many Internet sites and servers use cookies. Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID. A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie. It consists of a character string through which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored. This allows visited Internet sites and servers to differentiate the individual browser of the data subject from other Internet browsers that contain other cookies. A specific Internet browser can be recognized and identified using the unique cookie ID.

Through the use of cookies, this Website can provide the users of this website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without the cookie setting.

By means of a cookie, the information and offers on our website can be optimized with the user in mind. Cookies allow us, as previously mentioned, to recognize our website users. The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users to utilize our website. The website user that uses cookies, e.g. does not have to enter access data each time the website is accessed, because this is taken over by the website, and the cookie is thus stored on the user’s computer system. Another example is the cookie of a shopping cart in an online shop. The online store remembers the articles that a customer has placed in the virtual shopping cart via a cookie.

The data subject may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies through our website by means of a corresponding setting of the Internet browser used, and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. If the data subject deactivates the setting of cookies in the Internet browser used, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.

### Third Parties

Our website employs the use the various third party services. Through the use of our website, these services may place anonymous cookies on the Visitor’s browser and may send their own cookies to the Visitor’s cookie file. Some of these services include, but are not limited to: Google, Facebook, Twitter, Sucuri, Stablehost, StackPath and other social networks, advertising agencies, security firewalls, analytics companies and service providers. These services may also collect and use anonymous identifiers such as IP Address, HTTP Referrer, Unique Device Identifier and other non-personally identifiable information and server logs.

You may opt-out from Google’s cookies using their [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). You may also use the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt-out of some third party cookies.

### What are your choices regarding cookies

If you’d like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

  * For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: <https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050>
  * For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835>
  * For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>
  * For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple: <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US>
  * For any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.

### Where can you find more information about cookies

You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites:

  * AllAboutCookies: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
  * Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

## The rights of Users

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

  * Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  * Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
  * Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  * Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  * Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
  * Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  * Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  * Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

### Details about the right to object to processing

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

### How to exercise these rights

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User’s Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### How “Do Not Track” requests are handled

This Website does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

## Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Website and can request that the Owner remove the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Owner has about Users.

**Hosting of the Site**

This website is currently hosted in the United States. We are hosted on a server provided by HawkHost inc. For information about HawkHost and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.hawkhost.com/Legal/privacy).

## Definitions and legal references

### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

#### User

The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.

#### Data Subject

The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Website.

#### This Website

The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.

#### Service

The service provided by this Website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application.

#### European Union (or EU)

Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.

#### Cookies

Small piece of data stored in the User’s device.

## Owner and Data Controller

Rejoinweb Limited – 7 Florinis Street – Greg Tower, 2nd Floor –  
P.O. Box 23383 (or 24854) – 1065 Nicosia – Cyprus

Owner contact email: info@rejoinweb.com

### Legal information

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on the Site in place of the old version. You can identify the date that this Privacy Policy was last updated by looking at the date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting to the Site. Use of the Site following posted changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.thenamemeaning.com/contact-us/).

## Terms of Service

To review our Terms of Service, click [_here_](https://www.thenamemeaning.com/terms-of-use/).

## History

Latest update: May 25, 2018
